{"problemsArray": [
  {"alternatives": ["32(-2x + 1)", "-32(2x - 1)"], "answer": "32(-2x + 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 32, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -2x + 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-64x + 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "27", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 54 and 81\nThe factors of 54 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18, 27, 54\nThe factors of 81 are:\n1, 3, 9, 27, 81\n27 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n54, 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["7(2x - 3)", "-7(-2x + 3)"], "answer": "7(2x - 3)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 7, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 2x - 3 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n14x - 21", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 5)(x^2 + 5)", "-(x + 5)(-x^2 - 5)", "(-x - 5)(-x^2 - 5)", "-(-x - 5)(x^2 + 5)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x^2 + 5)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 5x^2) + (5x + 25)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 5) + 5(x + 5)\nx + 5 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 5)(x^2 + 5)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 5x) + (5x^2 + 25)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 5x^2 + 5x + 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 5, 13, 65", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 65\nEach number that divides evenly into 65 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n65", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["2(-x + 6)", "-2(x - 6)"], "answer": "2(-x + 6)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 2, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x + 6 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-2x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "6", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 42 and 6\nThe factors of 42 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 14, 21, 42\nThe factors of 6 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6\n6 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n42, 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 4\nEach number that divides evenly into 4 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["12(x + 1)", "-12(-x - 1)"], "answer": "12(x + 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 12, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with x + 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n12x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["6(10x - 1)", "-6(-10x + 1)"], "answer": "6(10x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 6, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 10x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n60x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["16(-x + 1)", "-16(x - 1)"], "answer": "16(-x + 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 16, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x + 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-16x + 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 7, 14", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 14\nEach number that divides evenly into 14 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["9(-8x - 1)", "-9(8x + 1)"], "answer": "9(-8x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 9, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -8x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-72x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["9(-8x + 3)", "-9(8x - 3)"], "answer": "9(-8x + 3)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 9, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -8x + 3 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-72x + 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["16(-4x - 3)", "-16(4x + 3)"], "answer": "16(-4x - 3)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 16, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -4x - 3 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-64x - 48", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 8", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 8\nEach number that divides evenly into 8 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9, 12, 18, 36", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 36\nEach number that divides evenly into 36 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["8(x - 6)", "-8(-x + 6)"], "answer": "8(x - 6)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 8, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with x - 6 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n8x - 48", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 2)(x^2 + 5)", "-(x + 2)(-x^2 - 5)", "(-x - 2)(-x^2 - 5)", "-(-x - 2)(x^2 + 5)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x^2 + 5)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 2x^2) + (5x + 10)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 2) + 5(x + 2)\nx + 2 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 2)(x^2 + 5)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 5x) + (2x^2 + 10)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 2x^2 + 5x + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["18(-3x - 4)", "-18(3x + 4)"], "answer": "18(-3x - 4)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 18, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -3x - 4 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-54x - 72", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x^2 - 5)", "-(x - 3)(-x^2 + 5)", "(-x + 3)(-x^2 + 5)", "-(-x + 3)(x^2 - 5)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x^2 - 5)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 3x^2) + (-5x + 15)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 3) - 5(x - 3)\nx - 3 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 3)(x^2 - 5)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 5x) + (-3x^2 + 15)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 3x^2 - 5x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 8)(x^2 - 8)", "-(x - 8)(-x^2 + 8)", "(-x + 8)(-x^2 + 8)", "-(-x + 8)(x^2 - 8)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 - 8)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 8x^2) + (-8x + 64)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 8) - 8(x - 8)\nx - 8 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 8)(x^2 - 8)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 8x) + (-8x^2 + 64)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 8x^2 - 8x + 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["8(-8x - 1)", "-8(8x + 1)"], "answer": "8(-8x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 8, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -8x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-64x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["16(5x + 2)", "-16(-5x - 2)"], "answer": "16(5x + 2)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 16, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 5x + 2 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n80x + 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["6(3x - 2)", "-6(-3x + 2)"], "answer": "6(3x - 2)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 6, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 3x - 2 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n18x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["8(-6x + 5)", "-8(6x - 5)"], "answer": "8(-6x + 5)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 8, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -6x + 5 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-48x + 40", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 1)(x^2 - 6)", "-(x + 1)(-x^2 + 6)", "(-x - 1)(-x^2 + 6)", "-(-x - 1)(x^2 - 6)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x^2 - 6)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + x^2) + (-6x - 6)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 1) - 6(x + 1)\nx + 1 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 1)(x^2 - 6)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 6x) + (x^2 - 6)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + x^2 - 6x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 24", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 24\nEach number that divides evenly into 24 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 7, 14, 28", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 28\nEach number that divides evenly into 28 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["3(-7x + 3)", "-3(7x - 3)"], "answer": "3(-7x + 3)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 3, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -7x + 3 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-21x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x^2 - 10)", "-(x - 6)(-x^2 + 10)", "(-x + 6)(-x^2 + 10)", "-(-x + 6)(x^2 - 10)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x^2 - 10)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 6x^2) + (-10x + 60)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 6) - 10(x - 6)\nx - 6 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 6)(x^2 - 10)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 10x) + (-6x^2 + 60)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 6x^2 - 10x + 60", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x^2 + 2)", "-(x - 6)(-x^2 - 2)", "(-x + 6)(-x^2 - 2)", "-(-x + 6)(x^2 + 2)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x^2 + 2)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 6x^2) + (2x - 12)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 6) + 2(x - 6)\nx - 6 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 6)(x^2 + 2)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 2x) + (-6x^2 - 12)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 6x^2 + 2x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "2", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 2 and 16\nThe factors of 2 are:\n1, 2\nThe factors of 16 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8, 16\n2 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n2, 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "3", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 3 and 3\nThe factors of 3 are:\n1, 3\nThe factors of 3 are:\n1, 3\n3 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n3, 3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 3)(x^2 - 2)", "-(x + 3)(-x^2 + 2)", "(-x - 3)(-x^2 + 2)", "-(-x - 3)(x^2 - 2)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x^2 - 2)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 3x^2) + (-2x - 6)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 3) - 2(x + 3)\nx + 3 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 3)(x^2 - 2)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 2x) + (3x^2 - 6)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 3x^2 - 2x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "2", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 16 and 18\nThe factors of 16 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8, 16\nThe factors of 18 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18\n2 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n16, 18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 18\nEach number that divides evenly into 18 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["4(4x - 5)", "-4(-4x + 5)"], "answer": "4(4x - 5)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 4, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 4x - 5 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n16x - 20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["40(2x - 1)", "-40(-2x + 1)"], "answer": "40(2x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 40, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 2x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n80x - 40", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "15", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 15 and 30\nThe factors of 15 are:\n1, 3, 5, 15\nThe factors of 30 are:\n1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 10, 15, 30\n15 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n15, 30", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 9)(x^2 - 7)", "-(x - 9)(-x^2 + 7)", "(-x + 9)(-x^2 + 7)", "-(-x + 9)(x^2 - 7)"], "answer": "(x - 9)(x^2 - 7)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 9x^2) + (-7x + 63)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 9) - 7(x - 9)\nx - 9 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 9)(x^2 - 7)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 7x) + (-9x^2 + 63)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 9x^2 - 7x + 63", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["12(-2x + 1)", "-12(2x - 1)"], "answer": "12(-2x + 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 12, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -2x + 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-24x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 6", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 6\nEach number that divides evenly into 6 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["2(x - 7)", "-2(-x + 7)"], "answer": "2(x - 7)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 2, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with x - 7 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n2x - 14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "7", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 63 and 28\nThe factors of 63 are:\n1, 3, 7, 9, 21, 63\nThe factors of 28 are:\n1, 2, 4, 7, 14, 28\n7 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n63, 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)", "-(x - 4)(-x^2 - 6)", "(-x + 4)(-x^2 - 6)", "-(-x + 4)(x^2 + 6)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 4x^2) + (6x - 24)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 4) + 6(x - 4)\nx - 4 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 6x) + (-4x^2 - 24)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 4x^2 + 6x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 2)(x^2 - 2)", "-(x - 2)(-x^2 + 2)", "(-x + 2)(-x^2 + 2)", "-(-x + 2)(x^2 - 2)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x^2 - 2)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 2x^2) + (-2x + 4)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 2) - 2(x - 2)\nx - 2 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 2)(x^2 - 2)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 2x) + (-2x^2 + 4)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 2x^2 - 2x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["14(-4x - 1)", "-14(4x + 1)"], "answer": "14(-4x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 14, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -4x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-56x - 14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 8, 16", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 16\nEach number that divides evenly into 16 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 8)(x^2 + 10)", "-(x - 8)(-x^2 - 10)", "(-x + 8)(-x^2 - 10)", "-(-x + 8)(x^2 + 10)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 10)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 8x^2) + (10x - 80)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 8) + 10(x - 8)\nx - 8 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 8)(x^2 + 10)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 10x) + (-8x^2 - 80)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 8x^2 + 10x - 80", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 5, 10, 20", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 20\nEach number that divides evenly into 20 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "7", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 21 and 28\nThe factors of 21 are:\n1, 3, 7, 21\nThe factors of 28 are:\n1, 2, 4, 7, 14, 28\n7 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n21, 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 32\nEach number that divides evenly into 32 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["6(-x - 1)", "-6(x + 1)"], "answer": "6(-x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 6, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-6x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 8", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 8\nEach number that divides evenly into 8 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "2", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 8 and 6\nThe factors of 8 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8\nThe factors of 6 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6\n2 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n8, 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 10)(x^2 + 5)", "-(x - 10)(-x^2 - 5)", "(-x + 10)(-x^2 - 5)", "-(-x + 10)(x^2 + 5)"], "answer": "(x - 10)(x^2 + 5)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 10x^2) + (5x - 50)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 10) + 5(x - 10)\nx - 10 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 10)(x^2 + 5)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 5x) + (-10x^2 - 50)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 10x^2 + 5x - 50", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["2(6x + 7)", "-2(-6x - 7)"], "answer": "2(6x + 7)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 2, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 6x + 7 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n12x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 7", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 7\nEach number that divides evenly into 7 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "8", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 40 and 64\nThe factors of 40 are:\n1, 2, 4, 5, 8, 10, 20, 40\nThe factors of 64 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32, 64\n8 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n40, 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "4", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 8 and 20\nThe factors of 8 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8\nThe factors of 20 are:\n1, 2, 4, 5, 10, 20\n4 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n8, 20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 7 and 8\nThe factors of 7 are:\n1, 7\nThe factors of 8 are:\n1, 2, 4, 8\n1 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n7, 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x^2 + 1)", "-(x + 4)(-x^2 - 1)", "(-x - 4)(-x^2 - 1)", "-(-x - 4)(x^2 + 1)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x^2 + 1)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 4x^2) + (x + 4)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 4) + (x + 4)\nx + 4 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 4)(x^2 + 1)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + x) + (4x^2 + 4)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 4x^2 + x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9, 12, 18, 36", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 36\nEach number that divides evenly into 36 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 14, 21, 42", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 42\nEach number that divides evenly into 42 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["30(-x + 1)", "-30(x - 1)"], "answer": "30(-x + 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 30, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x + 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-30x + 30", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)", "-(x - 4)(-x^2 - 6)", "(-x + 4)(-x^2 - 6)", "-(-x + 4)(x^2 + 6)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 4x^2) + (6x - 24)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 4) + 6(x - 4)\nx - 4 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 4)(x^2 + 6)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 6x) + (-4x^2 - 24)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 4x^2 + 6x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["32(-x - 1)", "-32(x + 1)"], "answer": "32(-x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 32, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-32x - 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 24", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 24\nEach number that divides evenly into 24 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["2(-10x + 7)", "-2(10x - 7)"], "answer": "2(-10x + 7)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 2, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -10x + 7 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-20x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "12", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 24 and 36\nThe factors of 24 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 24\nThe factors of 36 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9, 12, 18, 36\n12 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n24, 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "6", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 42 and 12\nThe factors of 42 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 14, 21, 42\nThe factors of 12 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 12\n6 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n42, 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "5", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 25 and 35\nThe factors of 25 are:\n1, 5, 25\nThe factors of 35 are:\n1, 5, 7, 35\n5 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n25, 35", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 3, 9", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 9\nEach number that divides evenly into 9 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["80(x - 1)", "-80(-x + 1)"], "answer": "80(x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 80, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n80x - 80", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "12", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 48 and 60\nThe factors of 48 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 16, 24, 48\nThe factors of 60 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 10, 12, 15, 20, 30, 60\n12 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n48, 60", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 10)(x^2 + 8)", "-(x + 10)(-x^2 - 8)", "(-x - 10)(-x^2 - 8)", "-(-x - 10)(x^2 + 8)"], "answer": "(x + 10)(x^2 + 8)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 10x^2) + (8x + 80)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 10) + 8(x + 10)\nx + 10 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 10)(x^2 + 8)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 8x) + (10x^2 + 80)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 10x^2 + 8x + 80", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 32\nEach number that divides evenly into 32 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 4", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 4\nEach number that divides evenly into 4 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["6(7x - 4)", "-6(-7x + 4)"], "answer": "6(7x - 4)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 6, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 7x - 4 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n42x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 12", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 12\nEach number that divides evenly into 12 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "6", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 18 and 48\nThe factors of 18 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18\nThe factors of 48 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 16, 24, 48\n6 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n18, 48", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "6", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 18 and 6\nThe factors of 18 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18\nThe factors of 6 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6\n6 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n18, 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 1)(x^2 - 9)", "-(x - 1)(-x^2 + 9)", "(-x + 1)(-x^2 + 9)", "-(-x + 1)(x^2 - 9)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x^2 - 9)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - x^2) + (-9x + 9)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 1) - 9(x - 1)\nx - 1 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 1)(x^2 - 9)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 9x) + (-x^2 + 9)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - x^2 - 9x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 1)(x^2 - 7)", "-(x + 1)(-x^2 + 7)", "(-x - 1)(-x^2 + 7)", "-(-x - 1)(x^2 - 7)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x^2 - 7)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + x^2) + (-7x - 7)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 1) - 7(x + 1)\nx + 1 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 1)(x^2 - 7)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 7x) + (x^2 - 7)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + x^2 - 7x - 7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 10)(x^2 + 10)", "-(x - 10)(-x^2 - 10)", "(-x + 10)(-x^2 - 10)", "-(-x + 10)(x^2 + 10)"], "answer": "(x - 10)(x^2 + 10)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 10x^2) + (10x - 100)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 10) + 10(x - 10)\nx - 10 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 10)(x^2 + 10)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 10x) + (-10x^2 - 100)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 10x^2 + 10x - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 18\nEach number that divides evenly into 18 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["4(-x - 5)", "-4(x + 5)"], "answer": "4(-x - 5)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 4, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -x - 5 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-4x - 20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["7(8x - 3)", "-7(-8x + 3)"], "answer": "7(8x - 3)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 7, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with 8x - 3 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n56x - 21", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 2, 5, 10", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 10\nEach number that divides evenly into 10 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n10", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["6(-4x + 9)", "-6(4x - 9)"], "answer": "6(-4x + 9)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 6, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -4x + 9 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-24x + 54", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 2)(x^2 + 2)", "-(x + 2)(-x^2 - 2)", "(-x - 2)(-x^2 - 2)", "-(-x - 2)(x^2 + 2)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x^2 + 2)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 2x^2) + (2x + 4)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 2) + 2(x + 2)\nx + 2 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 2)(x^2 + 2)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 2x) + (2x^2 + 4)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 2x^2 + 2x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["8(-5x - 6)", "-8(5x + 6)"], "answer": "8(-5x - 6)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 8, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -5x - 6 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-40x - 48", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 6)(x^2 - 6)", "-(x + 6)(-x^2 + 6)", "(-x - 6)(-x^2 + 6)", "-(-x - 6)(x^2 - 6)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x^2 - 6)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 + 6x^2) + (-6x - 36)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x + 6) - 6(x + 6)\nx + 6 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x + 6)(x^2 - 6)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 - 6x) + (6x^2 - 36)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 6x^2 - 6x - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "6", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 30 and 24\nThe factors of 30 are:\n1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 10, 15, 30\nThe factors of 24 are:\n1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 12, 24\n6 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n30, 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "1, 5, 25", "explanation": "Start from 1 and work your way up until you reach 25\nEach number that divides evenly into 25 is a factor.", "question": "Find the factors of:\n25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x^2 + 6)", "-(x - 6)(-x^2 - 6)", "(-x + 6)(-x^2 - 6)", "-(-x + 6)(x^2 + 6)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x^2 + 6)", "explanation": "Group the polynomial into two pairs\n(x^3 - 6x^2) + (6x - 36)\nFactor both groups individually\nx^2(x - 6) + 6(x - 6)\nx - 6 is a common factor. \nFactor it out to get the answer\n(x - 6)(x^2 + 6)\nNote: You can group as follows and get the correct answer.\n(x^3 + 6x) + (-6x^2 - 36)", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 6x^2 + 6x - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": [null,null,null,null], "answer": "3", "explanation": "Find the greatest common factor of 6 and 9\nThe factors of 6 are:\n1, 2, 3, 6\nThe factors of 9 are:\n1, 3, 9\n3 is the largest factor shared by the two", "question": "Find the greatest common factor of:\n6, 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["2(-8x + 9)", "-2(8x - 9)"], "answer": "2(-8x + 9)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 2, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with -8x + 9 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n-16x + 18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["63(x - 1)", "-63(-x + 1)"], "answer": "63(x - 1)", "explanation": "First find the GCF between the two coefficients, 63, and then pull that out of the expression so you end up with x - 1 as the expression.", "question": "Factor:\n63x - 63", "type": "text"}
]}